So then, which one of you is my foe?
Raven Black Hero!
I am Evileye, of the Blue Rose!
As a fellow adamantite class adventurer,
I request that we party up!
Wait, what's the point
of asking for his help?
I can't very well let his life be taken, too.
Understood.
May I begin by asking your name, please?
My name is Jaldabaoth.
Jaldabaoth? Well, all right. I am Momon,
adamantite class adventurer.
What is your purpose here?
It seems that a mighty item that can
summon us and make us do its bidding
has found its way into this city.
I am here for the purpose of recovering it.
He's trying to get information out of him
through this interchange, is he?
He's a first-rate adventurer, all right.
Demiur--
Ahem, Jaldabaoth, is there no other way
but for us to oppose each other?
No, there is not.
I realize that fairly well. In that event,
I will have to defeat you, right here.
You have no issue with that, do you?!
I am afraid I can't have that,
so I will have to resist.
Here goes!
Amazing... What is that?
Is that...?
But my heart stopped
beating a long time ago...
Hang in there, Lord Momon.
Miss Tuare, come, this way.
Are you all right?
Very well, let's get out of here while
Lord Sebas has the enemy drawn away.
Is something the matter, Lord Brain?
Hmm? Oh, no.
Let's go.
Zero?!
That's right, kid.
I remember seeing your face before.
You're Brain Unglaus, right?
Which means that Succulent was beaten
because he was outmatched.
In recognition of your
extraordinary talent with the sword,
let me offer you a chance.
Kneel before me,
and swear that you will
become my subordinate.
Do so, and I'll let you live.
Then you can die!
Zero, I'll be the one to take you on.
Climb, I'll let you handle
the enemy to the rear.
You've got it.
Figured it out, did you?
The way you slipped around
behind me like you did,
anyone could have smelled a rat.
Although, I had my doubts
ever since I saw you in the cell.
Hmph, so it was all a cheap trick, eh?
Succulent, kill those two
small-timers behind you.
You can at least do that, right?
O-Of course I can, Boss!
We meet again, huh,
kid?
Hey, now. I hear that top-notch monks' fists
can become as hard as iron,
but this is beyond even that.
I'll back you up!
This is the way a thief fights!
Poison?!
Powder of Will o' Wisp.
Thank you very much!
Damn it!
Martial Art! Ability Release!
Hmph! Damn it, Succulent!
On the other hand, Unglaus,
you have done quite well.
You may be the first man to ever
withstand my attacks for as long as this.
As are you.
Then what if we were to start fighting
like we mean it just a bit?
That sounds good to me.
That thing you're doing
is a sword barrier, right?
If I am careless enough to step too close,
I'll be cut in half, won't I?
However, I can tell that
you can only do that technique
by standing still, on the defensive.
Brain Unglaus, is that your ace in the hole?
That it is.
A slashing attack uses both Field,
which never misses,
and my speed-of-god blade attack, God Flash.
Blade Technique, Whistling Wind!
I'm going to punch right through
that technique and hit you.
I am the strongest in the kingdom!
So this is where you are.
Wha--?! What is going on?
The other Six Arms were
supposed to be dealing with you!
I have defeated all of your colleagues.
There's no way you could have
gone up against them
and come this far unharmed!
The truth is often taken
to be a surprising thing.
Lord Sebas, the Tuare that was
in the basement was a fake!
We have to hurry and go save her!
Thank you very much for your concern.
However, it is all right.
Tuare, please wait here for a moment.
Right.
Brain Unglaus, my fight with you
is on hold for now.
I'm going to show this old geezer
the power of Six Arms.
Geezer! You will pay for
these shenanigans with your life!
Panther!
Falcon!
Rhinoceros!
Buffalo!
Lion!
Wh-What are you...?
Whew, that was a close call.
It would seem that I was just
the slightest bit stronger, though.
Aspect of the Devil: Tentacle Wings!
Thank goodness you weren't hurt.
Y-Yeah...
Ah, your shoulder! Are you all right?!
Something this minor is no problem at all.
Never mind me,
I'm just relieved that you're all right.
Bravo. Imagine, being able
to keep her from any harm.
I, Jaldabaoth, would like
to sincerely offer you my praise.
I don't need your flattery.
Wah! L-Lord Momon?!
Forgive me, bards of the world!
Knights do fight while defending
their delicate maidens in their arms!
This feels more like
being baggage than a princess...
No, no, this is no time
to be thinking anything so silly!
Well, I think it's time I be on my way.
Our objective is an item.
I will now encircle a section of
the capital city in the flames of hell.
If you make your way inside, I promise you,
purgatorial flames
will send you into the afterlife!
Th-This is bad, Lord Momon!
We have to get him, quickly!
We can't. If we go after him,
he will start fighting like he really means it.
If that happens...
Ah! Lord Momon, you're protecting me...
Okay then, what am I going to do now?
So then, we drove the insect maid
right down to the ground.
You drove her?
And did you kill her?
No, we didn't kill her.
Jaldabaoth showed up before we could.
Is that right?
I see, I see--
Ahem! So um, couldn't it be
that Jaldabaoth got serious with you
because you were about
to kill the insect maid?
We tugged on the tiger's tail
when we shouldn't have.
That's what you're trying to say, right?
Jaldabaoth did say one thing--
He was going to envelop
part of the capital in hellfire.
There's no way a maid that was
in his service is on the up-and-up.
I believe my friends were right
to challenge her to battle.
Er, yes... you're right.
What you're saying is correct.
Pardon me.
Ah, please, lift up your head!
A man as handsome as you are shouldn't be...
Handsome?! What am I saying?!
Ah, but I can't help it, can I?
It's okay for me to have girlish thoughts
for the first time in hundreds of years,
isn't it? When he's this strong?
Yes! He's a handsome warrior
who's even stronger than I am!
Miss Evileye?
Y-Yes, um...
I need to discuss something with Nabe.
Excuse me a moment.
Huh?
She won't be able to hear us here.
Nonetheless, we should still be cautious.
Now then, Nabe...
I can pretty well guess
what Demiurge's plan is, in large part.
However, the more precise a machine is,
the easier it is to make it all come apart
by throwing a monkey wrench in the gears.
We must prevent
the slightest misunderstanding
from knocking everything back to square one.
Do you know what I mean?
Indeed. I would expect no less
from the Supreme One.
I have everything well in hand.
Like hell I do. I was called out here
in the first place by a request
from some grand nobleman
named Marquis Raeven.
We had to ride on a Floating Board,
and were carried along like luggage.
But, since the reward
was exceptional, that was fine.
And, because of
the disturbance here, I thought,
"This is the adventurer Momon's
first big fight in the capital city,
so I have to make a cool entrance,"
and jumped down from there.
Ugh, how did things turn out this way?
Now, I want you to get
in touch with Demiurge.
The reason I don't do it myself
is that I can't use magic right now.
Also, I have that girl's eyes on me.
Hmph, she's watching.
She must have her doubts about me.
You cannot mean it.
That is not the case, I daresay.
If I were to guess, could it not
be due to some other emotion?
Precisely why I do mean it. I can read
her thoughts like the back of my hand.
Becoming upset when she spoke
of Entoma was a critical mistake.
I should have expected as much, Lord Ains.
Truly, your vision befits
one who sits upon the throne.
Enough with the flattery.
It's an obvious consideration
that arose from my own slip-up.
Now, let's get the ball rolling, Narberal.
Yes, my lord.
Message.
That should keep my reputation
as the leader from falling apart.
Now then...
You know, it's hard to believe
that a little child like that
possesses adamantite class strength.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Would you like me to help you carry them?
My friends should be along shortly.
It's possible that we will be able
to cast resurrection magic right here.
Ho, you have someone
that can use resurrection magic?
Oh, uh, yes. Our team leader,
Lakyus, can invoke Raise Dead,
which is a 5th tier spell.
Will they be able to engage in combat
right after they return to life?
I'm afraid not.
This magic costs a huge amount
of life force at the time of resurrection.
Ho-ho...
As such, they won't be able to
physically move about very well for a while.
So much so that when it's cast
on those with lower life forces,
they will be reduced to ashes,
so it can't be used.
I see. If you wouldn't mind,
could we wait here with you?
I would like to meet this woman, Lakyus.
Wh-Why do you want to meet Lakyus?!
Sure enough, she's acting wary.
Well, um, I would like to meet
the leader of the Blue Rose,
a fellow adventurer,
and my senior in experience.
Is there some reason why I should not?
N-No! No, there's no problem!
Mr. Momon...
...please look over there.
What will you do after this, Lord Sebas?
I will take Tuare to a safe location,
to make sure that
nothing like this ever happens again.
Very well. Lord Sebas, thank you
for what you've done these last two nights.
Please do not let it concern you.
Someday, I will repay the debt
I owe you for helping to save her.
A wall of flame?
What is that?
The flames of Gehenna?
My good adventurers,
thank you for coming together
in this time of crisis.
Early this morning, a wall of flame
sprang up around this area of the capital.
These flames are similar to an illusion,
and coming into contact with them
seems to do no harm.
The leader of the Blue Rose
has in fact confirmed this.
I actually touched it.
I didn't feel the least bit of heat,
and went inside without
any interference at all.
I also confirmed that there are low-level
demons on the other side of the wall.
The ringleader behind this incident
is named Jaldabaoth.
We have information that he is
an extremely fiendish and powerful demon,
who has many other evil entities serving him.
Just how strong is he?
Two of my comrades,
the warrior Gagaran and the thief Tia,
were killed by him.
And it only took him one blow, at that.
--What?!
--One blow?!
Don't lose your heads!
Jaldabaoth is strong, to be sure.
As someone who actually confronted him,
and was powerless to stop him,
I can assure you of that.
However, we have this man on our side!
The Raven Black Hero, Master Momon!
Yes. We are absolutely not going
into a fight that we cannot win.
Now, allow me to present
our detailed plan of attack...
Lastly, we will need a detached force
to rescue the civilians
who are trapped inside the wall of flame.
If the demons are holding them captive,
they will likely use one of
the warehouse districts inside the wall.
They'll split up families,
to keep them from breaking out.
Climb, you'll go, right?
As you wish. Even if it costs my life.
Princess,
would it be okay if I went along, too?
Are you sure, Lord Brain Unglaus?
Well, count me in, too.
All right, everyone, I will remain here,
praying to God that
every last one of you comes back.
Good hunting!
Leave it to us!
Long live the Golden Princess!
Climb...
I'll lend you this.
What is it?
A magic item?
Yeah. It's supposed to raise one's power
as a warrior well past their limits.
Past their limits?
I-I can't accept such a precious item!
I myself got it from an old lady I know.
Bring it back to me alive.
We all have to come back,
for the princess's sake.
Right!
Form a line using the adventurers,
and have the guardsmen back them up,
to thin out the enemy's formation...
Then have the greatest force,
consisting of the raven-black Momon
and Nabe, as well as Evileye,
acting as an arrowhead
to break through the enemy's center.
But isn't Climb's mission a dangerous one?
He will be making rounds inside the capital,
together with your soldiers, won't he?
It will be no different for him.
Climb may end up dead,
but if he does, Lakyus will cast
her resurrection magic on him.
Then, when his life force
is drawn out by the magic,
who will look after the weakened Climb?
Who could object to nursing back to health
someone who followed orders to his death,
and then came back to life?
So that's it.
All according to plan, my sister?
Yes.